No, you don't have to do it again.
You have already done it.
But it is very important when you go ...
I weigh 33.80.
Yes.
It is great that they are in control of-
Or, it is important that they are in control of your weight when you go with a small propeller plane.
Yes, so it doesn't get really strange ...
- Uneven weight.
- Yes.
Paula and Flora are with us today, but the rest of the family is in school and jobs.
Ulrik is not in school.
- No, he's at work.
Yes, he works from home today.
- What much warmer it was here.
- Yes indeed.
A newly awake Laura.
Then I think this is that she wants a pacifier, I don't think they know what it is right.
Or, they may know what it is, but there is nothing anyone here has.
(English) - How is it?
- Well thanks.
Self?
(English) Good.
(English) - Oh, strong.
- Strong man.
Now the tassels are very uneven, but you get two tassels anyway.
So.
- So!
- See, Laura.
- Lots of children.
- Yes, there are lots of children here now.
- Where should we put it?
- Here's back.
You do not consume it but you reflect it with clean water, it is very important.
Then you fill this bucket with dirty water.
It is important to put the filter in the right direction.
And then at the other end, it slowly runs out completely clean water.
When there is a stop reversing the filter, and then you can start using it again.
(English) - Where does this water come from?
- From a water reservoir south.
- And that's not clean.
- No.
It contains hair and algae.
Okay.
- You are a little curious about what they say.
- Yes, the giant sneaky.
They talk about the technology.
- (Laura) Bath there.
- No, not swim there, Laura.
That water is dirty and it should be purified now, so people can drink it without getting sick.
Do we have any cup, then?
Or a glass?
- Okay water?
- Yes, now the water is clean, Laura.
When it comes out of the filter.
(English) Is it okay?
Great.
(English) Top.
- What a thing!
- Yes, what a thing.
(The camels are grunt)
They look so happy.
They have as well as upstairs.
- But then, isn't it an exciting pasture they have built?
- Yes.
With bare branches.
- Figured branches.
- But very small, maybe.
- Yes.
- They seem a little nervous.
They may not like to be in front of the camera.
(The camels are grunt)
- Probably not.
- Or they have a stomach ache.
- Do you think they are fine, Laura?
- Yes.
So, I am getting crazy about Laura having a pacifier in her mouth all the time.
But then just recently she picked up a stone.
Then she removed the pacifier and was about to put the stone in her mouth.
(English) Hello!
We had no idea that this was waiting for us.
Oh, what a nice thing.
I will go with you.
I'm here.
Should we sing along, Alma?
Stop it.
I know, I'm embarrassing.
And very sweaty.
But I'm happy.
This was fantastic!
Yes indeed.
- I get tears in my eyes from this.
- Why?
There will be so much emotion!
There will be so much emotion.
(English) - Wow, thank you very much!
- Thanks!
Wow!
(Alma) Oh, wow!
MAF collaborates with many aid organizations, but is the enabler for help to arrive.
Yes exactly.
So now it's a QR code on the screen here.
If you open Swish you can donate a little gift.
Yes.
Such a filter costs about SEK 400 \ HKR.
But then the transport itself is out to these incredibly distant places ...
But I think as always: many streams small.
What if everyone watching this video gives 1 \ Hkrona?
Yes.
- There will be many water filters and transport, I promise you.
- Yes.
- Why did I hold here?
- I do not know.
You paw a little at me.
- I felt your heart.
- Oh, I'm kissing your glasses.
God...
- We have never done anything like this before.
It feels a bit ... - It's a lot of emotions.
Yes.
You feel so insecure when you are in such a place.
You don't know ...
On the one hand, we do not know how it will land with you.
But at the same time it feels just right.
We feel very privileged because we have been given the chance to follow this trip.
- You get it.
- And we got that.
- You on it.
- Yes, this one was actually for you, Laura.
Should I have it?
TA-DA!
Oh wow!
The family's own massage.
- Not massage - they are rendille.
- Yes exactly!
- The massages had the same blankets.
- I know.
We have learned so much on this trip.
I had no idea.
I had no idea before we got here.
Really.
Don't ruin it!
- But I think this is a foot link.
- Yes, but she has to address this first.
- Well.
- We put it on your foot.
But Alma, this is our last vlog from Africa.
How would you summarize Kenya and what we have been through?